(Leonard:)He's right, I was thinking
of the lower flermin.
(Raj:)Ooh, I'll, uh, text Stuart,
let him know we're close.
(Bernadette:)That's a neat tattoo.
(Emily:)Oh, thanks, it's Sally from
Nightmare before Christmas.
(Bernadette:)Aw, that movie's
so cute.
(Howard:)Do you like her because
you both have red hair?
(Emily:)Uh, a little, but more
that she's covered in scars
(Emily:)and can pull her own limbs off
and sew them back on.
(Bernadette:)I like Cinderella.
(Emily:)Did you know,
in the original book,
(Emily:)the sisters cut off
their toes with knives
(Emily:)in order to fit
in the glass slipper?
I like "Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo."
(Raj:)Hey, here comes
Stuart and his date.
(Emily:)Oh, she's cute.
(Howard:)Oh, my God.
(Leonard:)What?
(Howard:)That's Jeanie.
That's Jeanie?!
(Emily:)Who's Jeanie?
Don't say it.
(Raj:)That's Howard's cousin
that he had sex with.
(Howard:)She is my second cousin.